Sonic and Manic can one of you please go
check for mailbox I have to keep
watching the meatloaf so that it does
not burn how about you sucks my balls
and get me a root beer you dumb
how about you sucks my bro you should
then talk to our mom like that
well errands you gonna say sorry oh my
God you guys it'll just go get it oh my
God Sonja you sit you were asked back
down don't let Sonic treat you like his
like he's doing to Mum I will go
get the mail Goddammit
Oh oh my God is this is this a coupon
for one free bean and cheese burrito
from Taco Bell oh my God I can't believe
this and with extra beans and
cheese oh oh oh my oh yes
Sonya Sonic come check this out
what the hell Gong keep oops my show was
just getting to the good part and now
you're stinking up the house with your
smelly ass oh my God what's that
smell oh wait that's just your ass now
what the do you want
fine then I guess I'm going to keep this
all for myself I'm going to take a
crap
what's you got there in your pocket
gunky poops oh my God
hat hat hat hat hat off donkey poops you
cannot escape the clutches of this fat
blue Hedgehog Huff Huff Huff oh
help meee EEE heavy huh now give me the
coupon the chess mom Sonic and Manic are
fighting again don't try to stop them
Sonia they will just gang up on you like
last time
[Applause]
come on Knuckles hurry the up and
answer the damn phone hello
M cackles the cool Echidna who is this
it's me Sonia
okay cool how is it going my home east
Kelley G biscuit ah
Knuckles can you kick my process of
course I can but not now in watching my
favorite Sonic Underground episode
episode 28 no Hedgehog is an island are
you sure Knux my mom is making
meatloaf oh my God it'll be there in a
Mobius minute
you
come on in the door is open
hey Sonia hope you don't mind I brought
some of our friends alone for why Sonic
why why do you do this
it was just a burrito coupon you
you you fat-ass lie you fat-ass
why oh my God at that as Sonic
really is here I bet he already ate the
meatloaf come on guys
let's blow this popsicle stand wait
everyone stop it please
Sonic my bro it appears that we both
want this free burrito coupon as you may
know I will not just hand it over to the
likes of you my fat bro what are you
saying I'm saying that we stand at a
crossroad and there is only one way to
settle this the usual the usual
bro I'm sure you remember the rules
course I do gunky poops we each take
turns picking our team mates one by one
I of course will pick my lover
Bartleby Mundell care of Dresden hah
Bartleby
as if that will do you any good
dah well there are no way you can win my
bro because I pick Knuckles for my
partner bro you just picked him cause he
black no bro I picked him because he's
my friend not like you know what a
friend is
oh my God I can't believe it
I've never been picked for anything in
my entire life
holy I think I'm going to my
pants Kiki says what chicks c'mon Knux
what's taking so long
um I don't have a basketball uniform
don't worry Knux you can use my old
one from high school you are smaller
than me so it might be able to fit
well in Knux it actually fits held to
the yaw unfortunately
hey Knuckles what do you want you dumb
think fast my turn to pick I'm
gonna have to pick someone good to make
up for Bart levy not playing what do you
mean that he's not going to play simple
Gunks of course Bartleby would just make
you all look like noobs
he says he's so good that he only makes
the final shot
whatever your loss who to pick Mindy's
dad bro you know Mindy's dad isn't
allowed he will just push everyone on
the ground like last time you you can't
be serious I sure as hell am it everyone
else sucks balls Sonia you actually know
some about basketball right Manik
always talks about basketball and
you have to know something come on Sonia
you're on my team me oh well oh please
God no
Sonia you get your ass down here right
now bro leave our sister alone shut up
gunky poops or I will shove this
basketball up your ass I'd like to see
you try you fat why why do we
always fight nice job bro now you made
our sister cry she's only crying because
you're so fat
[Music]
it's
tyranny father
[Music]
man
where God
[Music]
[Applause]
get famous how the system
[Music]
I'm sorry bro I guess I did get kinda
out of hand
you sure did fat-ass but you're my bro
so I guess we are cool looks like it's
going to be a two versus two cool come
on Knuckles we need to make up a plan
for the game oh all right
Knuckles hurry up my black homie